Guide to the Willard Dickerman Straight papers, 1825-1925.
Straight, Willard Dickerman papers, 1825-1925.
- Visual Materials
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Von Ketteler Arch, Peking 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba Korea
    - Gardens 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - China, Peking 1092-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Architectural Detail 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Architecture, Exterior 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Architecture, Interior 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Bland, John O.P. 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - China, Manchuria 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - China, Manchuria, Newchwang 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Cornell U. 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Cuba, Havana 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Cuba, Santiago-de-Cuba 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Great Wall 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Korea 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Longworth, Alice R. 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Longworth, Nicholas 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Morgan, Edwin V. 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Railroads 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Sculpture 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Straight, Willard D. 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Temple of Heaven, Peking 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Temples 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Tombs 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Transportation, Railroads 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - U.S. Legation, Havan 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Vendors 1902-1912 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Cuba, Korea
    - Summer Palace n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Agriculture 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Architecture, Interior 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Bland, John O.P. 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Bridges 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Casenave, Maurice 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Chinese Army 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - German Consulate, Mukden 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Hart, Robert 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Holwill, Claude N. 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Japanese Army 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Korea, Seoul 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Longworth, Alice R. 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Longworth, Nicholas 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Marvin, George D. 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Mezger, Otto 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Ming Tombs 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Occupations 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Paddock, Gordon 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Palaces 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - People 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Railroads 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Russia, Siberia 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Russia, Vladivostok 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Russo-Japanese War 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Street Scenes 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Sze, Sao-Ke Alfred 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Temple of Heaven, Peking 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Tombs 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Transportation, Carriages 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Transportation, Railroads 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Trans-Siberian Railroad 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Winter Scenes 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - China, Manchuria, Siberia, Korea (annotated by George Marvin)
    - Yalu River 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - German and English Architecture (commercial photographs)
    - Germany n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - City Scenes 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Korea 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Korea, Seoul 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Landscapes 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Maritime Scenes 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Morgan, Edwin V. 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Paddock, Gordon 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Pagodas 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Chinese 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Koreans 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Portraits 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Railroads 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Rural Scenes 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Russian Navy 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Russo-Japanese War 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Sculpture 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Ships 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Street Scenes 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Transportation, Railroads 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, China, Korea (annotated)
    - Von Ketteler Arch, Peking 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, Japan, China, and Korea (annotated)
    - Camel Caravans 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, Japan, China, and Korea (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, Japan, China, and Korea (annotated)
    - Japan 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, Japan, China, and Korea (annotated)
    - Japanese Army, Officers 1904-1905 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China (annotated)
    - Ceylon 1901 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China (annotated)
    - Morrison, George E. 1901 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Individuals 1901 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China (annotated)
    - Street Scenes 1901 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China (annotated)
    - Transporation, Oxcarts 1901 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Peking Social Aquaintances (annotated)
    - China, Peking 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Peking Social Aquaintances (annotated)
    - Conger, Edwin H. 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Peking Social Aquaintances (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Peking Social Aquaintances (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Individual Westerners 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Portraits
    - People, Unidentified Westerners 1902 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Portraits
    - Portraits 1902 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Portraits
    - China 1902c (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Social Aquaintances
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1902 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Social Aquaintances
    - China 1902c (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Social Aquaintances
    - Social Life 1902c. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - China, Manchuria 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Rural Scenes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Street Scenes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Railroads, Construction 1905 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Agriculture 1905 c. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - China 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Occupations 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Rural Scenes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Transportation, Horsecarts 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Transportation, Horses 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Russo-Japanese War Correspondence (annotated)
    - Palmer, Frederick 1903-1905 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Russo-Japanese War Correspondents (annotated)
    - McCormick, Frederick 1903-1905 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Russo-Japanese War Correspondents (annotated)
    - People, Individual Westerners 1903-1905 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Russo-Japanese War Correspondents (annotated)
    - Pershing, John J. 1903-1905 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Steet Scenes
    - Transportation, Streetcars 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Street Scenes
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Koreans 1905 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Street Scenes
    - Railroads 1905 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Street Scenes
    - Dress 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Street Scenes
    - Korea 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Street Scenes
    - Street Scenes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Street Scenes
    - Transporation, Oxcarts 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Street Scenes
    - Transportation, Railroads 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Cathedral
    - Architecture, Exterior 1905 c. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Cathedral
    - Cathedrals 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Cathedral
    - Ceremonies 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Cathedral
    - China 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Architectural Detail n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - China n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Ming Tombs n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Pagodas n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Sculpture n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Towers n.d. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - China, Manchuria n.d. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - China, Peking n.d. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Palaces n.d. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Architecture
    - Summer Palace n.d. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Boats and Ships (annotated)
    - Boats n.d. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Boats and Ships (annotated)
    - China n.d. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Boats and Ships (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria, Antung n.d. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Boats and Ships (annotated)
    - Seascapes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Boats and Ships (annotated)
    - Ships n.d. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Bridges, Gates, Arches
    - Arches n.d. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Bridges, Gates, Arches
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Bridges, Gates, Arches
    - Bridges n.d. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Bridges, Gates, Arches
    - China n.d. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Bridges, Gates, Arches
    - Gates n.d. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Agriculture n.d. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Rural Scenes
    - China n.d. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Rural Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Agriculture 1905 c. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Camel Caravans 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Rural Scenes
    - China 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Landscapes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Rural Scenes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Transportation, Ferries 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Street Scenes
    - China 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Street Scenes
    - Occupations 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Street Scenes
    - Street Scenes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Street Scenes
    - Transportation, Horsecarts 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Street Scenes
    - Village Scenes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Early Career
    - China, Nanking 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Early Career
    - China, Peking 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Early Career
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Early Career
    - Portraits 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Early Career
    - Von Keteler Arch, Peking, Dedications 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Early Career
    - Von Ketteler Arch, Peking, Construction 1901-1902 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Russo-Japanese War
    - City Scenes 1904-1905 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Russo-Japanese War
    - Japanese Army 1904-1905 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Russo-Japanese War
    - Russo-Japanese War 1904-1905 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Manchurian Scenes
    - Railroads 1904 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Manchurian Scenes
    - Architecture, Exterior 1904 c. (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Manchurian Scenes
    - China, Manchuria 1904c. (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Manchurian Scenes
    - Street Scenes 1904c. (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Manchurian Scenes
    - Transportation, Railroads 1904c. (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Chinese Scenes
    - Construction n.d. (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Korea
    - Children 1904c. (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Korea
    - Japanese Army 1904c. (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Korea
    - Korea 1904c. (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Korea
    - Street Scenes 1904c. (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Gates
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Buildings and Gates
    - China n.d. (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Buildings and Gates
    - Gates n.d. (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Buildings and Gates
    - Street Scenes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Street Scenes
    - China, Manchuria 1908c. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Street Scenes
    - City Scenes 1908c. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Street Scenes
    - Markets 1908c. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Street Scenes
    - Occupations 1908c. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Street Scenes
    - Street Scenes 1908c. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Street Scenes
    - Transportation, Horsecarts 1908c. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Children 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Landscapes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Occupations 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Rural Scenes 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Rural Scenes
    - Transportation, Horsecarts 1905c. (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Harbors n.d. (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Seascapes n.d. (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Ships n.d. (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Transportation, Barges n.d. (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Transportation, Steamships n.d. (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Lumber n.d. (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Occupations n.d. (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Ships n.d. (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Transportation, Barges n.d. (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Transportation, Rafts n.d. (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Rivers and Ships
    - Transportation, Steamships n.d. (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Charles J. Arnell, U.S. Consulate, Mukden (annotated)
    - Priests 1907 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Charles J. Arnell, U.S. Consulate, Mukden (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1907 c. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Charles J. Arnell, U.S. Consulate, Mukden (annotated)
    - Arnell, Charles J. 1907 c. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Charles J. Arnell, U.S. Consulate, Mukden (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Charles J. Arnell, U.S. Consulate, Mukden (annotated)
    - Korea, Seoul 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Charles J. Arnell, U.S. Consulate, Mukden (annotated)
    - Temples 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Charles J. Arnell, U.S. Consulate, Mukden (annotated)
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Charles J. Arnell, U.S. Consulate, Mukden (annotated)
    - U.S. Legation, Seoul 1907c. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Boats 1908 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Landscapes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Lumber 1908 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - River Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Tombs 1908 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Chinese Army, Infantry 1908 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Chinese Army, Officers 1908 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Gillis, J.V. 1908 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Government Officials 1908 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Transportation, Horsecarts 1908 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Chinese Army 1908 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Chinese Army, Officers 1908 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Gillis, J.V. 1908 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Military Training 1908 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Bamboo 1908 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Gillis, J.V. 1908 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Government Officials 1908 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - River Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Village Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Manchurian Trip(annotated)
    - Boats 1908 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Chinese Army, Light Artillery 1908 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Military Training 1908 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Chinese Army, Officers 1908 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Landscapes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Village Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Landscapes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - River Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Village Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Agriculture 1908 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Landscapes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Transportation, Horses 1908 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Manchurian Trip
    - Village Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Gillis, J.V. 1908 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Government Officials 1908 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Street Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Transportation, Horses 1908 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Village Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Transportation, Horses 1908 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Agriculture 1908 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Escort 1908 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Landscapes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - River Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Transportation, Ferries 1908 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Village Scenes 1908 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - Walls 1908 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Manchurian Trip (annotated)
    - China, Manchuria 1908 (Box 62, Folder 39)